lacrossepinnies.com 2018-12-31

# Privacy Policy - Lightning Wear Apparel - Custom Made Sports Wear

Lightning Wear takes your information that you provide on our site very serious. Below is our privacy policy statement with regards to the information you give us on the site. Feel free to contact us with any privacy or personal information concerns at 888-438-7875.

[](https://www.lacrossepinnies.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2017/10/small_bolt-1-e1507911073448.png)**privacy policy**

Our Commitment to Privacy **[Lightningwear.com](https://www.lightningwear.com/ "Lightning Wear")** and **[LacrossePinnies.com](https://www.lacrossepinnies.com/ "Lacrosse Pinnies")** respects the privacy of its customers and strives to maintain customer confidence. We collect customer information in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, contests and promotions. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties.  All information obtained in connection with the processing and ordering of your item is safe and secure.    Our site is protected and monitored by Godaddy SSL Certificate.

This policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it and when we share it with third parties. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information.

* * *

**If you have any questions about our privacy policy, you can always contact Lightningwear.com   and LacrossePinnies.com customer service in any of three ways:**

**1\. send us an email to  info@lightningwear.com.**

**2\. call us at 1-888-GET-STRK (1-888-438-7875)**

**3\. write to us at**

**Lightning Wear Apparel Inc.**

**Customer Service**

**10580 Metropolitan Avenue**

**Kensington, Maryland 20895 USA**

* * *

Any information changes in the future will be posted immediately on our website. Revision dates will always be placed at the end of the policy. You may exercise your choices about how we collect and use your information at any time.

## Privacy Policy FAQs

### **What kind of information does Lightningwear.com collect?**

We collect information, such as name, e-mail and postal addresses, phone and credit card numbers from you when you visit our website or one of our stores, place an order online or by phone, save your info with us online, or participate in a contest, promotion or survey.

### **How does Lightningwear.com use my information?**

When you place an order or make a purchase from Lightningwear.com, we use your personal information to process your order, send you e- mails to confirm your order or to contact you via phone, postal mail or e-mail if we have other questions regarding your order or purchase.

From time to time, we may use this information to contact you via e-mail, postal mail, or telephone to learn more about your shopping preferences. You always have the choice not to receive marketing information or calls.

### **Does lightningwear.com share my information with third parties?**

Lightningwear.com does not sell any of your personal information provided on our site to any third partiers. LW reserves the right to disclose information about you as required by law, in response to legal process and law enforcement requests, and as necessary to protect the property, interests and rights of Lightningwear.com, its affiliates, and others.

Lightning Wear Apparel manufactures custom sports uniforms and apparel for all sports. This includes uniforms for lacrosse, football, basketball, baseball, soccer, track and field, tennis, golf, field hockey, intramural teams, fraternity and sorority sports, club teams and youth sports. Grade schools, youth sports leagues, middle schools, high schools, Colleges, Community Colleges, and Universities play hard and win in Lightning Wear.

## LACROSSE APPAREL

For lacrosse, over the past five years, we have outfitted many college lacrosse teams, high school lacrosse teams, club lacrosse teams, intramural lacrosse teams, fraternity lacrosse team and sorority lacrosse teams. REVERSIBLE PRACTICE JERSEY. We specialize in custom team **[lacrosse uniforms](https://www.lacrossepinnies.com/blog/lacrosse-uniforms/)** , lacrosse jerseys, lacrosse shorts, reversible lacrosse jerseys, mesh lacrosse pinnies, reversible lacrosse pinnies, lacrosse shorts, lacrosse shirts, shooting shirts and performance under gear.

## SOCCER APPAREL

We are not just a lacrosse company.  Lightning Wear also manufactures custom soccer apparel  and soccer team uniforms.  Our **[soccer jerseys](https://www.lacrossepinnies.com/blog/maroon-soccer-jerseys/)** can be made in any style or design. We also make custom soccer shorts for youth and adult teams.  Our **[kids soccer uniforms](https://www.lacrossepinnies.com/blog/kids-soccer-uniforms/)** can be made in sizes as small as youth extra small.

## WOMENS APPAREL

For women, we produce two styles of lacrosse uniforms and womens kilts. They are racer back lacrosse jerseys and [capped sleeve lacrosse jerseys](https://www.lacrossepinnies.com/blog/girls-sublimated-lacrosse-jerseys/ "capped sleeve lacrosse jerseys"). Ladies we also sell womens lacrosse pinnies as well. Lightning Wear manufactures ladies lacrosse shorts and ladies lacrosse skirts or kilts. We make all lacrosse apparel in mens, womens and youth sizes. Our team is lucky to outfit many youth lacrosse leagues, youth lacrosse associations, youth lacrosse camps, and youth lax games across the globe.

## YOUTH APPAREL

Our youth apparel is made for all sports.  We can produce custom youth lacrosse uniforms, youth lacrosse pinnies, youth lacrosse shorts, youth reversible jerseys, youth lacrosse shirts, and youth warm ups and jackets. Lightning Wear has partnered with many youth lacrosse association parents across the United States. We can handle lacrosse apparel packages and spirit wear. Lacrosse packages include hooded sweatshirts, sweat pants, lacrosse custom t shirts, lacrosse practice shorts, lacrosse warm up suits and lacrosse golf shirts. We offer in house custom printing and embroidery on all merchandise. Lacrosse summer camps, lacrosse tournaments, YOUTH REVERSIBLE PRACTICE JERSEY, CUSTOM REVERSIBLE PRACTICE JERSEY.

## BASKETBALL APPAREL

For Basketball, we sell custom basketball uniforms, custom mesh basketball practice jerseys, custom basketball shorts, basketball shooting shirts, basketball warm ups, basketball practice pennies, basketball practice pinnies, short sleeve basketball t-shirts, **[long sleeve basketball shirts](https://www.lacrossepinnies.com/blog/long-sleeve-basketball-shirts/)** , basketball hoodies, basketball hooded sweatshirts, basketball sweat pants, sweat pants with pockets, basketball shorts with pockets, custom basketball uniforms, custom reversible basketball uniforms. Youth basketball uniforms, youth basketball jerseys, youth basketball shorts, youth basketball programs, womens basketball uniforms, mens basketball uniforms, college basketball uniforms. We work with many basketball youth associations, basketball leagues, basketball summer camps, basketball practices, basketball tournaments. Custom numbered basketball jerseys made on site.

Thank you for reading our privacy policy information page.  We operate our manufacturing facility seven days a week.  For any general business or manufacturing questions. please contact us at 888-438-7875.  Our team stands ready to serve you.

TAGS

Ladies Field hockey and ladies lacrosse. **[Custom field hockey uniforms](https://www.lacrossepinnies.com/blog/girls-field-hockey-pinnies/ "Custom field hockey uniforms")** , custom field hockey skirts, custom field hockey shorts, custom field hockey kilts. Womens field hockey hoodies, womens field hockey sweats, womens field hockey warmups, womens field hockey performance apparel, custom field hockey jersey, girls field hockey uniforms, youth field hockey uniforms, womens field hockey numbered jerseys. Womens lacrosse jerseys, womens lacrosse uniforms, womens field hockey leagues. Youth field hockey associations, youth field hockey leagues, youth field hockey tournament, youth field hockey camps, youth lacrosse camps, youth summer lacrosse camps. Reversible lacrosse jerseys, reversable lax tank tops. Senior pinnies, senior tank tops, senior reversibles, senior pennies.

### Basketball Shorts

Design and order custom basketball shorts in adult and youth sizes.  
Made to order in Maryland, USA  
 **Custom Basketball Uniforms**

### Basketball Sweatshirts

Design and order custom basketball sweatshirts in adult and youth sizes.  
Made to order in Maryland, USA  
 **Custom Basketball Uniforms**

### Basketball Jerseys

Design and order custom basketball jerseys in adult and youth sizes.  
Made to order in Maryland, USA  
 **Custom Sublimated Basketball Uniforms**

### Basketball Shooter Shirts

Design and order custom basketball shooter shirts in adult and youth sizes.  
Made to order in Maryland, USA  
 **Custom Youth Basketball Uniforms**

### Long Sleeve Basketball Shooter Shirts

Design and order custom long sleeve basketball shooters shirts in adult and youth sizes.  
Made to order in Maryland, USA  
 **Custom Adult Basketball Uniforms**
